No... Not there...
Hurry up and climax already, jeez.
N-No, Kizuna-kun, that's my...
I guess this is the right spot.
But, you know,
you sure are sensitive, Himekawa.
Th-That's not true!
I-I'm just doing this because
it's part of our mission!
I'll finish it now!
Take this!
No!
Yes!
Heart Hybrid successful!
Charging is complete, Himekawa!
You're finally out.
Yurishia!
Your Heart Hybrid always
takes so long, Hayuru.
Well, you were having a good time, I suppose.
Th-That's crass slander!
I would never do something
as perverted as this...
...b-because I wanted to!
Okay, okay. I get it.
Anyway, now that you've recharged,
get to work.
Of course!
Neros!
See you.
Aine!
Aine?
A-Aine-san?
What do you think you're doing?
It's supposed to be my turn next!
No fair, Aine!
Talk about an annoying crowd.
Wha—
Aine?
Kizuna, do it with me right now.
Huh? But your Hybrid Count is still high.
To change the course of
this battle, I want...
...the forbidden weapon.
But that's...
Don't worry, Kizuna.
I am who I am.
No matter what happens, that won't change.
So do it with me...
Let's Climax Hybrid.
Episode One
Strategic Defense Academy Ataraxia
W-Wait, Mom!
Goodbye, Kizuna.
You're not needed anymore.
If I'm having a dream like that,
I must be nervous after all.
Seriously, what is Sis planning?
Dear Kizuna,
I filled out all the paperwork
for you to attend Ataraxia.
Come to Ataraxia immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Reiri.
I hear from her after ages,
and that's all she says?
Though, well, I came anyway,
so I'm one to talk.
To Ataraxia
Arriving at Ataraxia now.
Please have your ID ready
for the border crossing.
Welcome to Ataraxia.
So this is the integrated research facility
that's been training people and doing R&D
to fight the otherworld invasion,
Strategic Defense Academy Ataraxia.
Are you a transfer student?
Hello there!
That's Yurishia-sama for you.
You can say that again.
Hey!
Wait!
I can't ignore something so lewd!
So I'm going to be living here now?
It doesn't seem real...
The guy who just ran by
must've dropped this.
H-Hello?
Kizuna, did you make it here okay?
Sis!
Yeah, just now.
But is it really okay
for me to come to Ataraxia?
My grades aren't that great,
and I was already kicked out of here once.
I don't want to hear your excuses!
I need you,
and your Heart Hybrid Gear.
What are you talking about?
It's not going to be useful for anything now.
Shut up and get your ass to HQ, Kizuna Hida!
I always get what I want!
And I want that thing that was
installed in you, the Er—
I-I'm coming!
I'm on my way,
so please don't say another word!
I'm lost...
Wh-Where is HQ?
Who are you?
U-Um...
Do you lack the intelligence
required to understand language?
I've never seen a creature like you before.
Uh, I'm Kizuna Hida.
From now on, I'll be going
to the high school here.
You're a student here, right?
What else could I be?
Do you think I'm a weirdo who got a
uniform and snuck through security,
just so I could look at the scenery?
You don't need to be so touchy.
Touchy?
Why would I waste my time
being touchy with you?
It would make more sense for you
to get on your knees and beg me.
To let you kiss my feet.
I'm not gonna beg for that!
You're lying, you inferior creature.
What's with this girl?
She's hot as hell,
but her personality's not so swell.
I'm Aine Chidorigafuchi, from Class 2-A.
Now worship me!
Hell no!
Sheesh...
An air-raid siren?
An air raid?
This place is supposed
to be in the safe zone.
Their ships shouldn't be
able to travel this far.
This is Ataraxia.
There'd never be a false alarm here.
The enemy really has appeared.
The enemy...
You need to run.
W-Wait!
What are you doing?
What is someone sees you?
The only one watching is you!
I told you to run, you lecher.
Y-You're the one who started stripping,
you exhibitionist.
Just look away. That way,
there won't be a problem.
Right now, I'm a poor victim,
and you're a perverted Peeping Tom.
Who are you calling a pervert?
A pilot suit?
You can't be...
Zeros!
A Heart Hybrid Gear!
She has a core installed, too?
Aine Chidorigafuchi,
your Heart Hybrid Gear
has little charge left.
You can't fight for long.
You don't have to spell out the obvious.
A Magitech weapon?!
I should go, too.
What's all that stuff doing here?
I guess normal weapons
wouldn't work after all.
Sh-She hit it?
What an absurd fighting style.
There's an interception system here, too?
Wow!
You just defeated a Magitech with
a normal weapon and your bare hands.
These things are everywhere?
Of course.
We never know when the enemy will attack.
And fighting Magitech weapons
is Amaterasu's mission!
Amaterasu...
They never learn.
Evacuate quickly.
If you don't, you'll die.
Shouldn't I fight, too?
You're not needed anymore.
Hard work means nothing
without the talent to back it up.
Talent can be honed, but if there's nothing
to hone in the first place...
There's nothing that can be done.
Sure,
my Heart Hybrid Gear has very little power.
But if I equip it, maybe I can do something.
Er... Er... Er...
I can't do it!
I can't say that name!
Blade!
What's an off-campus student doing here?!
This is an emergency!
You have a Hybrid Gear, too?
Hey!
We'll be in trouble if we all don't fight,
so could you please not slack off?
Oh, is that your boyfriend?
H-H-He couldn't possibly be my boyfriend!
How lewd!
We have a more important, more noble goal!
Okay, okay.
Let's go take out the descending
Magitech weapons, then.
If we don't hurry,
Ataraxia will be wiped out.
I know that!
You get to a shelter immediately!
Understood?
Those girls are fighting,
and I'm...
I can handle that, too...
My Hybrid Count...
What's happened to her?
A-Are you serious?
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
Listen, Kizuna.
A person's value isn't
decided by their abilities.
It's decided by how they live.
Sis!
Eros!
Make it in time!
Ow...
Sure, it may be useless junk,
but how can it be this weak?
Hey, Chidorigafuchi!
Pull yourself together!
Are you okay?
Damn it! What do I do?
Kizuna, can you hear me?
Sis! Is that you?
Good, I'm in a bad—
Shut up!
I know your situation.
If you want to save Aine, do as I say.
Fine. What should I do?
First, fondle Aine's breasts.
Okay.
What are you making me do?
Be gentler.
Fondle them like crazy, but gently.
No, I mean...
Why am I fondling a girl I just met?
Don't think! Feel!
Feel her heart and body.
Her heart and body?
If you can't do that, both of you will die.
If you want to get out of this situation
and save Aine, it's the only way!
Only you can do this, Kizuna!
Only me?
Then think of it this way.
Check her body for wounds.
Every nook and cranny.
O-Okay. I can do that.
Chidorigafuchi?
Just keep going!
O-Okay. Got it.
I-I never knew a girl's body was so soft.
Now spread her legs.
Get in between them and look. Carefully.
Okay.
It really just seems like
I'm feeling this girl up...
And...
No!
I-It's digging in so deep.
What was that shaking?
Did a cannon hit?
Hurry! There's no time!
I nearly chocked...
...to death...
Is this the light of her Heart Hybrid Gear?
She's so cute...
Now, Kizuna! Feel up her breasts!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm doing what you said...
Harder!
But that's not...
Just do it now, and do it hard!
Success!
Well done, Kizuna!
S-Success?
The Heart Hybrid was a success!
Heart Hybrid?
A mixing of heart and love.
That is the true power
of the Heart Hybrid Gear!
Are you okay?
Hey, Chidorigafuchi!
What did you do while I was unconscious?
I feel so light.
No way. My Hybrid Count...
It was almost zero.
Aine!
Commander! What is this?
I'll explain later. Can you fight?
Yes!
Zeros!
This power...
I can do it!
Chidorigafuchi?
She's crazy.
Wow!
That's amazing, Aine!
You defeated that huge army.
Yurishia! Hayuru!
Where's the enemy carrier?
Retreating...
Yes.
But we destroyed most of the
enemy Magitech weapons,
so let's be content with that.
But what happened?
Aine was like a totally
different person just now.
Oh?
Is that...?
Who...
...are you?
What was that?
For now,
we've made it through the first stage.
The mission is only just beginning,
but the Hybrid Heart is the key...
...to the success of this mission!
The key to retaking the mainland,
retaking the world we lost!
Illustration: Kana Miyai
What's with him?
How he could do that, or that, to me?
You'll pay for this, Kizuna Hida!
But if I can gain power that way, I...
Next Time: "Heart Hybrid"